http://www.olyarms.com/shop/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

Olympic Arms
Cart:
0 item(s) - $0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Search:
Search
Categories
HomeAccessoriesGripsAR15 Grips1911 Grips/StocksHandguardsFiberiteFree FloatingFront Sight OptionsGas BlocksFlip-Up SightsHarris Bi-PodsOA LogowareOptics - SightsToolsSight ToolsManualsPartsA2 Rear SightBarrel AssembliesBarrelBarrels - StandardBarrels - UltramatchBolt & CarrierButtstocksA2 ButtstockM4 CollapsibleReceivers & Receiver SetsParts AssembliesLower Receiver PartsAssembled Lower ReceiversPistol Caliber MagazinesPistol Caliber UppersUpper ReceiverMagazinesDIY Pro-ShopPistol Caliber PartsWSSM Parts.22-250 Parts7.62x39 PartsAR15 KITSOA93 PISTOL PARTSPistolsK24 11.5" AR15 PistolsK23P AR-15 6.5"OA93 AR15 PistolsAR-15 Pistol Caliber ModelsGlock® Series PistolsRiflesUMAR RiflesWSSM RiflesM4 SeriesK8 SeriesK16 SeriesEliminator SeriesAR-15 Carbines 16"AR-15 20-24"AR-15 LE ModelsGamestalkerPistol CaliberPistol Caliber CarbinesPistol Caliber AR Style PistolsUppersWSSM UppersPistol Caliber Upper ConversionsK16 Series UppersPistol Uppers (AR15)Pistol Caliber Pistol Length UpperSALES/CLOSEOUTSPistol BarrelsSig Sauer® Barrels1911
HomeAccessoriesGripsAR15 Grips1911 Grips/StocksHandguardsFiberiteFree FloatingFront Sight OptionsGas BlocksFlip-Up SightsHarris Bi-PodsOA LogowareOptics - SightsToolsSight ToolsManualsPartsA2 Rear SightBarrel AssembliesBarrelBarrels - StandardBarrels - UltramatchBolt & CarrierButtstocksA2 ButtstockM4 CollapsibleReceivers & Receiver SetsParts AssembliesLower Receiver PartsAssembled Lower ReceiversPistol Caliber MagazinesPistol Caliber UppersUpper ReceiverMagazinesDIY Pro-ShopPistol Caliber PartsWSSM Parts.22-250 Parts7.62x39 PartsAR15 KITSOA93 PISTOL PARTSPistolsK24 11.5" AR15 PistolsK23P AR-15 6.5"OA93 AR15 PistolsAR-15 Pistol Caliber ModelsGlock® Series PistolsRiflesUMAR RiflesWSSM RiflesM4 SeriesK8 SeriesK16 SeriesEliminator SeriesAR-15 Carbines 16"AR-15 20-24"AR-15 LE ModelsGamestalkerPistol CaliberPistol Caliber CarbinesPistol Caliber AR Style PistolsUppersWSSM UppersPistol Caliber Upper ConversionsK16 Series UppersPistol Uppers (AR15)Pistol Caliber Pistol Length UpperSALES/CLOSEOUTSPistol BarrelsSig Sauer® Barrels1911
Home
>
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Olympic Arms, Inc. (“OAI”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This policy describes our practices regarding personal and account information collected through our web site. In this policy, “personal and e-Account information” means your name, company name, account number, address, telephone number, and e-mail address plus other information that personally identifies you, including your industry, the number of employees at your company, and purchase history, and “we” and “us” means OAI. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy from time to time. Each version of our Privacy Policy is marked with a version number and effective date. We recommend that you visit our web site periodically to review any changes.
How much information must I share?
The amount and type of information we collect from you depends on your activities and use of our web site. Below, we explain what information we collect.
When you browse our web site
We may collect your IP address to measure our web site traffic and to help provide a relevant shopping experience. If you come to our web site via a link, we may collect the location of the link that referred you. We may collect information about the browser you are using to help optimize our web site for visitors. We may keep track of pages you visit to help provide you with a more personalized shopping experience.
When you make purchases through our web site
We collect your name, address and payment information to process your order. However, you may provide credit card and purchase order numbers by telephone. We may collect information contained in “cookies,” such as your purchases and login data, to personalize your shopping experience. Your browser may be required to accept cookies if you wish to add items to a shopping cart.
When you create an e-Account on our web site
We collect your user name, password, bill-to-address, and e-mail address. You can help us ensure your privacy by not sharing your user name or password.
When you subscribe to our e-mail newsletter through our web site
You must create an e-Account to subscribe to our e-mail newsletter. We use your e-Account information in connection with your subscription. You may unsubscribe by e-mailing the webmaster and following the instructions therein.
When you communicate with us through our web site
We collect your e-mail address and the other information that you provide in order to respond to your communication. When you enter contests, participate in surveys, or register for other activities on our web site We collect your name, e-mail address and telephone number, and the other information that is required for entry or participation, which varies depending on the activity. Our business partners may co-sponsor contests on our site. If you enter one of these contests our co-sponsors may receive the information collected or may collect the information directly. In these situations, we will tell you who is collecting your information, how they may use it and how to contact them.
How is my personal and e-Account information used?
We may use your personal and account information to provide products or services you have requested, respond to a communication from you, contact you, and as otherwise described in this policy. We may occasionally send you promotional or product information. If you do not wish to receive promotional or product information, you may opt out of future communications by following the instructions in the e-mail communication. In addition, in order to measure how we are doing and to better understand how we can improve our product offerings, we or one of our service providers or strategic partners may contact you by telephone or e-mail and solicit your participation in research. Your participation is voluntary. If you become our customer, we may send you updates on important information about our company and services.
How is my personal and e-Account information shared?
We restrict access to your personal and e-Account information to those who need access to use it as set forth in this policy, which includes franchisees and service providers who are restricted by confidentiality obligations. Only authorized personnel are permitted to see your E-Account password. We may share your personal and e-Account information with our third party services providers, including but not limited to our credit card processors, web site developers and hosts, advertising agencies, third party shippers and other services providers, whose use of your information is limited to providing services to us. We do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise share your personal information with others. We may disclose your personal and e-Account information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, as required by law, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. Your personal and e-Account information may also be disclosed in event of any future connection with a sale of some or all of our business or a merger with another company.
How do you protect my personal and e-Account information?
We use 256-bit encryption technology and Secure Socket Layers (“SSL”) in all areas where your personal and e-Account information is required. In addition, your personal and e-Account information and transaction history are kept behind our firewall on separate servers. All transaction information is processed under encrypted channels.
How do I edit or delete my e-Account information?
You may edit your account information at anytime by signing in to your account and clicking “Edit e-Account”. You can access, review and update your personal information. Your account can be deleted but doing so will result in not being able to access certain areas of the site. To delete your account, please call us at 1-800-228-3471 with specific instruction to delete your account.
How can I give you feedback or contact you?
You may contact us through the Contact Us section from our online web site. Please note that messages become our property and, unless you direct otherwise, may be used by us for promotional purposes. Comments or questions can also be sent to us via postal mail, and we will use reasonable efforts to promptly review and respond as appropriate: Olympic Arms, Inc. 624 Old Pacific Hwy SE Olympia, WA 98513
Information
About Us
Customer Service
Privacy Policy
Site Map
Search Terms
Advanced Search
Orders and Returns
Olympic Arms, Inc. All Rights Reserved.   |   Web Design provided by 855PROGEEK
